Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  - Student concerns: Academics, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Student concerns: Admissions, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Student concerns: Admissions, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Student concerns: Admissions, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Student concerns: Appeals, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Student concerns: Charles Levy Case, 1994-1995 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Student concerns: Complaints, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Student concerns: Complaints, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Student concerns: Complaints, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Student concerns: Course scheduling, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Student concerns: Course scheduling, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Student concerns: Financial aid, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Student concerns: Financial aid, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Student concerns: Financial aid, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Student concerns: Housing, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Student concerns: Housing, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Student concerns: Housing, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Student concerns: Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Student concerns: Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Student concerns: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Student concerns: J. Tumminia case, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Student concerns: Parking, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Student concerns: Parking, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Student concerns: Parking, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Student concerns: P. Sirotta, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Student enrollment, 1985-1990 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Student enrollment statistics and summaries, 1986-1995 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Student information system (SIS) project, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Student life task force, April 4, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - GMU student markets report, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Student services, 1986-1992 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Student services: AIDS, 1988-1991 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Student services: Greek housing, undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Student services: Substance abuse, 1990-1995 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - GMU strategic planning, 1987-1992 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Surveys and questionnaires, 1980-1981 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Surveys and reports, 1989-1994 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Task force and event scheduling, circa 1990 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Report of the task force on continuing education, June 1987 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Technology for literacy conference report, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Telephone message pad, February 20-March 24, year unknown (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, September 19-October 28, year unknown (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, October 24, 1988-March 13, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, October 31, 1988-December 7, 1988 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, December 7, 1988-January 20 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, January 12, 1989-June 19, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, January 20, 1989-February 20, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, March 24, 1989-May 3, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, June 15, 1989-August 7, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, May 3, 1989-June 15, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad, August 8, 1989-September 19, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Telephone message pad: Ann Wingblade, December 8, 1993-September 9, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Terrel Bell report "To secure blessings of Liberty", 1986 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - The Tower club, 1988-1995 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Travel, February 21, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - United Press Internation vs. GMU, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - University community (draft report), November 3, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - UCIS: Computer information systems, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - UCIS: Computing and information systems conference, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - UCIS: Guide to University computing and information systems, Fall 1991 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - UCIS: Review of the TSI report, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - UCIS: Strategic capabilities for computing and communications: Mason's four year plan 1991-1995, August 1, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - UCIS: Strategy for implementing the administrative information system, February 12, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - University life: Black Student Association, 1987-1996 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - University life: Creating faculty unity and strength through diversity (draft and final), 1992 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - University life: Counseling center, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - University life: General, 1993-1995 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - University life: Housing, 1994-1996 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - University life: Invitations, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - University life: Learning communities and multiple citizenship, interim report, 1990-1991 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - University life: Learning initiatives and community building (report), May 1994 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - University life: Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - University life: Organizations, miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - University life: Student government [1 of 3], 1994-1996 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - University life: Student government [2 of 3], Spring 1995 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - University life: Student government [3 of 3], Fall 1994 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - University life: Transition team: "Student services in support of learning, GMU looks to the future", 1995 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - University relations: Public statement regarding budget, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - GMU Update, October 1990 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Venture Virginia partners, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Virginia alcohol safety action program (VASAP), 1993 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1992-1997 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce; Board of Trade, 1991-1993 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Virginia code commission, 1993-1998 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Virginia community college system, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Department of Criminal Justice Services, 1992-1994 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Department of Education, 1991-1997 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Virginia economic development policy, 1992-1995 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Energy Plan: Evaluation survey, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Virginia facts and figures, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Initiative: Meetings and guestlists, 1986-1988 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Office of the Comptroller, 1994-1997 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Virginia Opera, 1994-1996 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - The Virginia Plan for Higher Education, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Amendments to Virginia Plan, 1986-1988 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - The Virginia Plan introduction and background, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - The Virginia Plan paper one: "A time of opportunity", 1985 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Virginia retirement system, 1990-1995 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - The Virginia survey: Results from statewide survey on higher education and environmental problems, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Washington airports task force, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC), January 1989 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC), 1992 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors, executive committee meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, February 16, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting agenda, May 31, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, May 31, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, September 20, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, September 20, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, November 8, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, November 8, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting agenda, January 17, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, September 12, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, November 14, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, November 27, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, April 17, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, July 31, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, November 20, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, March 12, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Board of Directors (BoD) meeting minutes, April 9, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Bylaws, March 1987 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Certification, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Correspondence, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Financial statements and audit, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Library information survey, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Library information survey, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Meeting WRLA, October 1, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC) Meeting, February 13, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Participant agreement, September 11, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Participant agreement, September 18, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Status report, February 1988 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Washington Research Libraries Consortium (WRLC): Summary of advantages and cost / benefits, December 1, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - WEEL radio station, 1983-1985 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Earl C. remarks, November 17, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Writer's seminars, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Series 7: Alan G. Merten, 1990-2004, (25 boxes)
  Alan G. Merten became the fifth president of George Mason University in July of 1996 and he has announced his retirement for June 2012. Series 7 "Alan G. Merten" includes documents from 1990-2004. Found within this series are papers concerning university athletics, economic development, partnerships, and conferences, as well as, correspondence and memoranda.
  - 123 Club, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - "A dialogue on sustaining the vitality of the National Research Enterprise", October 25-26, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Abell, Bess and Tyler (Merry-go-round farm), 1997 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol: Abuse policy, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol: "Changing the drinking culture on Campus", May-June 1998 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol: Promising practices: Campus alcohol strategies Task Force planner, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol task force, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Chi National Honor Society, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Lamda Delta, 2001 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Association: Reidy, Susan P., 1994-1996 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Alumni affairs: Cornell University, 1995-1996 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Alumni relations: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Alumni relations: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Alumni relations: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Alumni relations: Miscellaneous correspondence, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - America Online (AOL), 1998 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - America Online (AOL): Regional leadership collaboration meeting, July 17, 1998 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU), 1995-2000 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU) diversity, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - American Association of University Women, 1996-1999 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - American Council on Education, 1996 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - American Electronics Association, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - American Electronics Association, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - American Express, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - American Heart Association, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - American Management Systems, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - American Public Sector (SAP), 1998 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Andrulis Research Corporation, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Aquatic Center, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Arlington Campus, budget, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Arlington conference center task force, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Association of Black Faculty, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Association of Chinese Schools, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - AT & T, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Athletic highlights in the 1990s, July 22, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Athletics: Aimee Willard endowment fund, June 1996 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Athletics: Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), 1996-1998 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Athletics: Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), 1999-2000 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Athletics: Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), 2001 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Athletics: Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), correspondence on withdrawal of the University of Richmond, 2000 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Athletics: Colonial Athletic Association (CAA), Radford University appeal, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Athletics: Equity in athletics disclosure act, Fall 1996-Spring 1997 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Athletics: Intercollegiate athletics, 1995-1996 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Athletics: National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Athletics: National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), funding and revenue, 1997-2000 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Athletics: National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), reports, 1991-2001 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1998-1999 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Bennett, Peter; IMGMS, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Bennis, Warren article, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - BIRLA, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Bishop, Richard, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Bleicher, Sam, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Bloch, Eric, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Boeing, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Bryan III, John Stewart, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Bulgaria, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Business education taskforce, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Business executive for national security (BENS), 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Calendar, July 1, 1996-June 30, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Campus compact, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Capital campaign, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Capital one, 1998 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Capitol connection, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Carlyle group, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Center for innovative technology, 2000 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Center for minority excellence in technology (Comet), 2000 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Century club, 1992-1998 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Changing world of work, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Chesapeake region 2012 coalition [1 of 2], 2001 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Chesapeake region 2012 coalition [2 of 2], 2001 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - CEO directory, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Child development center, 1996 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Chopra, J.S. (India), 1998 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Christmas Cards, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Chronological correspondence, January 1996 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Chronological correspondence, March 1996 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Chronological correspondence, April 1996 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Chronological correspondence, May 1996 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Chronological correspondence, June 1996 (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Chronological correspondence, July 1996 (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Chronological correspondence, August 1996 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Chronological correspondence, September 1996 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Chronological correspondence, October 1996 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Chronological correspondence, November 1996 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Chronological correspondence, December 1996 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Chronological correspondence, budgetary priorities, December 1996 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Chronological correspondence, meeting with Northern Virginia delegation Board of Visitors, December 1996 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Chronological correspondence, miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Chronological correspondence, January 1997 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Chronological correspondence, February 1997 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Chronological correspondence, March 1997 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Chronological correspondence, April 1997 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Chronological correspondence, May 1997 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Chronological correspondence, June 1997 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Chronological correspondence, leadership Washington, June 1997 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Chronological correspondence, July 1997 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Chronological correspondence, August 1997 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Chronological correspondence, September 1997 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Chronological correspondence, Vienna-GMU WMATA designation, September 1997 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Chronological correspondence, October 1997 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Chronological correspondence, November 1997 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Chronological correspondence, faculty salaries, November 1997 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Chronological correspondence, Virginia microelectronics consortium, November 1997 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Chronological correspondence, December 1997 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Chronological correspondence, January 1998 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Chronological correspondence, February 1998 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Chronological correspondence, National Institute for the environment, February 1998 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Chronological correspondence, technology showcase thank you letters, February 1998 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Chronological correspondence, March 1998 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Chronological correspondence, Worldview by Eric Dent, March 1998 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Chronological correspondence, April 1998 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Chronological correspondence, Charles K. Rowley, April 1998 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Chronological correspondence, May 1998 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Chronological correspondence, June 1998 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Chronological correspondence, July 1998 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Chronological correspondence, George Mason University world congress, July-August 1998 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Chronological correspondence, August 1998 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Chronological correspondence, September 1998 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Chronological correspondence, October 1998 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Chronological correspondence, November 1998 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Chronological correspondence, December 1998 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - CIESIN annual report, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Civic engagement, 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Clinton - higher education, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - College drinking task force, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Commission/Commonwealth's plan and budget process, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Commission of the future of public education, November 1996 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth competition council, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth conference: the old dominion and the new economy, preliminary report, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia oracle partnership presented by Alan G. Merten, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Community foundation survivor's fund, December 3, 2001 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Congressional institute for the future, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Consortium of international earth science, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Consortium of Universities, 1998-1999 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Convocation, 2003 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Cook, Dr. C. Barrie, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Coopers and Lybrand, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran Museum, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Cornell-William Anderson, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Corporate relations, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Corporate universities, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Council for higher education, accreditation, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2000 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Council on competitiveness, 1998-2000 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Council on information management, 1995-1999 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Cranch, Edmund T., 1997 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - C-Span, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - CUPA compensation and benefits questionnaire, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - DARPA informational briefing, February 1997 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - De Benedetti, Carlo, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Delcommune, Michel-Marc, 1999 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Denning, Peter, 1996 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Department for the deaf and hard of hearing, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Development task force, 1997-2004 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - DigiGym Systems, Inc., 2001 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Digital divide, 2001 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - The Dilenschneider Group, July 2001 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Distance education and learning, 1995-1997 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Distributed university, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Distributed university, "The Wandwaver Solution", 1996 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - District of Columbia, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Earley, Mark, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - E-City, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Economic bridge, November 2000-October 2001 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Economic development, 1996-1997 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Economic development: BBR Virginia outlook, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Economic development: High education support for regional economic development, circa 1995 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Economic development: Virginia economic indicators, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - The economy of the District of Columbia and its impact on the Washington area, December 1996 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - EDS corporation, 1999-2000 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Election day, support Mason, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 10)